["It's like Whoa" playing]
♪ Whoa
Here we go ♪
♪ It’s solid gold
It's like whoa ♪
♪ I didn't know so much soul
♪ I think I like, I want some more
It’s like whoa ♪
♪ Got me got me feelin' like whoa ♪
♪ So excited feeling like I should
It's like…♪
Oh, look who's here!
Hi.
-You look like a married woman.
-Hi, doggies.
Marriage looks good on you.
-Thank you. It feels good.
-Good.
It was perfect.
[Chrishell] Tell us.
How was the wedding night?
[Mary] Stayed up for a bit--
-How long?
-[Mary] Had a good time.
-Oh my God.
-I want to know everything.
I'll leave some details for just us.
But I'm just glad it all came together.
The whole thing was perfect.
It couldn't have been more beautiful.
-[Amanza repeats] It was so gorgeous.
-[Chrishell] I loved it so much!
-People behaved themselves.
-That is shocking.
[Amanza] Well…
Nothing happened at the wedding, but…
Well, I was filling Amanza in
on the broker's open.
Apparently,
after you left the broker's open,
Christine went into the whole group
and was, like, mimicking you.
And, like, "She was acting
like a fucking idiot."
She never talks straight.
So when you don't talk straight,
that makes you look like a fucking idiot.
-How was I acting like an idiot?
-She was doing her impression of you…
[gasping]
She just… [gasping]
…and talks in circles. She was, like,
"Well, my sister was in town,
and this and that…" [stutters]
-And she wouldn't let it go.
-Wow.
Christine has really revealed
her true colors over the past year or so.
We were, like, ride or die,
and hearing that she called me
a fucking idiot is heartbreaking.
I just didn't think
she would be that person to me.
Who does that as a friend?
As a woman? As a grown woman?
-It's very rude.
-Just mocking. My kids don't mock people.
No. I mean, you don't say that
about a friend or anybody.
And then don't come the next day
and with flowers and apologize.
Oh, conveniently forgetting that part.
I wanted to come here
and apologize for being a total bitch.
When it comes to me and you,
I don't want fights or constant:
"Did you hear this?
Do you know what she said?"
I don't know.
To ask for forgiveness and then…
mock and make fun. I think it's crazy.
And Mary tends to let things blow over,
but Christine's shit?
It won't fly with me.
I think Christine's completely outta line.
And then has the balls to show up
at your wedding after, like,
talking shit about you to everybody,
and then to your face acting like…
-…she wanted to make everything all good.
-I didn't even think about that.
[scoffs]
[dramatic music rises and fades out]
♪ Now that I got your attentions
I forgot to mention this is my moment ♪
♪ I'm not trying to impress you ♪
♪ If you like what I do
This is just a preview ♪
♪ We do what we want
What we want ♪
♪ We do what we want ♪
♪ What we want
What we want ♪
♪ We do what we want ♪
♪ What we want
What we want ♪
♪ We do what we want ♪
♪ What we want ♪
-[Christine] Hey, babe.
-Hey.
-[Christine] How's it going?
-Good.
[repeating] Lookin' good.
-Good to see you.
-How are you?
[Christine] Honestly, I love real estate.
I'll always be in it.
But, you know,
I get a little distracted by my fiancé,
planning a wedding,
and our extended vacations.
But this is the type of house
that I get excited about.
It's sexy, it's fun, it's in a great area.
If there's anyone that's gonna sell a fun
house like this, might as well be me.
-[Kaz] What's up?
-Hey. Good to see you.
-This is Christine.
-Hi, how are you?
Kaz, nice to meet you. Simba.
[Christine] Hi, baby. Hi.
-Hi, how are you? Christine.
-Monika, pleasure. Hi, guys.
[Christine] Who's this?
-This is Simba.
-[Christine] Oh, cutie.
-[Kaz] Hey, Simba.
-[Christine] Wow! This is great, guys.
Monika wants to co-list
the property with us.
A co-listing is when a property
is represented by two different brokerages
or two different agents, and sometimes
it's very advantageous when you can have
multiple people working for your listing
to help get it sold.
-[Monika] Thanks for coming.
-It's gorgeous. Thanks for having us.
[Kaz] Sure, of course.
-For us to be a dual agency here.
-[Christine, Brett] Yeah.
Co-listings are generally not my thing.
I don't get along well with others.
I'm the more experienced agent,
so she needs to follow my lead
if she wants to get it sold.
Christine's one of our top agents,
and she knows this area really well.
She just sold a house down the street.
She'll be a great benefit to us.
-[Brett] Give us a little background.
-I bought this house back in 2012.
It was a tear-down,
and I built it from scratch, basically.
And then in 2016, we finished the house.
Monika brought up the idea to me.
Maybe you should look into listing it.
-Good job.
-[all laugh]
-Always.
-We love that idea, Monika.
That's why you don't date an agent.
-You'll never hold onto your properties.
-[Kaz] Lemme show you outside.
-Yeah.
-Yes, let's see it.
Wow, guys, this is stunning!
-[Brett] Cool.
-[Christine] Incredible. Is this LED?
[Kaz] Yes. It's actually built
on a hydraulic lift
-that goes up and down.
-[Christine] This is absolutely beautiful.
What kind of industry are you in?
I'm so curious.
-[Kaz] I'm a software engineer.
-Are you?
I used to own a software company,
but I set up my own construction company
-as a part of this.
-Wow.
We wanted the ceilings to actually be
16-feet high, but we had to settle at 14.
-Fourteen's pretty tall.
-Yeah.
You know what the AC bills are
in a 16-foot-high ceiling?
True, but a good thing is
I own a solar company,
so my entire electrical bill
for this whole house is like $22 a month.
Wow.
-The master bedroom.
-[Christine] Wow! Love it.
-[Monika] Open closet, as you can see.
-[Christine] I love the closet.
I love that the bedroom
overlooks the putting green with the view.
-This really is gonna sell the house.
-Thank you. Exactly.
[Christine] Can we play?
How do you do this?
-[Monika] Yes, we can try it.
-[Brett] Whoever gets closer
dictates the listing price. You go first.
[Brett] Okay.
-[Brett] You serious now?
-[Kaz] It went pretty good.
-That was so close.
-[Kaz] That was so close.
[Kaz grumbles]
-That was good too.
-That's a close one.
-Christine, you're up.
-Alright, if I get this goal…
-Goal?
-Whatever it's called. Then you're out
-and I got the listing. Deal?
-You can have what you want
-if you make that with a driver.
-[Christine laughs]
[all laughing]
-[Monika] Simba got it.
-Okay, golf's over. [laughs]
[Christine] He won,
so we're on this listing together.
So, I'm curious what you were thinking
in terms of price point.
-I'm sure you have something in mind.
-What I'm willing to let it go for
-is about six million dollars.
-Six is really high.
But I would go with five-three personally.
What is your opinion?
I think we should definitely start
with 5.495
and then just see what happens.
By pricing it lower,
it gives us the opportunity
to be in a potential bidding war situation
where you could get more than
you initially signed up for.
So I feel, like, let's be less aggressive
with the price if possible
to get as many people interested in.
'Cause I'd hate
-for this beautiful home to sit.
-It's gonna depend a lot
on what projects I can get into.
Alright, so…
-why don't we do 5.495 like you suggested?
-[Monika] Yeah.
That's a compromise. What offers
you accept are completely up to you.
We'll work on finding you
another opportunity.
So it's more enticing for you
to accept a reasonable offer.
-Okay.
-[Christine giggles]
-[Brett] Alright, cool.
-[Kaz, Monika] Sounds good. Thanks.
[Brett] Yeah, pleasure.
Monika seems nice,
but nice doesn't really sell houses.
So I'm hoping her and I
can work together to get this sale done,
but it seems like I might be
taking the reins on this one.
["Number One" playing]
♪ Walk all of the walks
And yeah I'm talking all the talks ♪
♪ I can play it nice
But I can also do it bad ♪
♪ Come in nice and close
I'll be the best you ever had. Ha! ♪
-[music fades out]
-[cell phone rings]
-Hi.
-[woman] Hello.
How is everything?
[Heather] Good. I'm at the office early
before everyone.
It's actually really peaceful and quiet.
[laughs]
[Maya] I bet.
Once all of them come in, it's like a--
-[Maya] I know.
-…hurricane.
Speaking of hurricanes, I'm in Miami.
Thankfully, none here.
We miss you.
I know. I have to come back
for an ultrasound check, so…
-Is everything--
-And also-- No, it's all good.
Pregnancy is going well.
I'm three months along,
and I still go back and forth
between LA and Miami.
But being away from the office
is at times better
because I just want to avoid the tension.
How is everything at the office
with Mary and Christine?
I mean, I know how Christine is.
She does take it sometimes too far.
It is what it is. I mean…
I say things and then I'm like, "Shit,
I shouldn't say that. Fine, I'm sorry."
-You get away with it because you're Maya.
-Because of my accent?
-[Heather] Yeah.
-[Maya] So here is my advice;
if you're making
a second bachelorette party, Heather,
-we better be invited.
-Of course. All the girls will be invited.
Yeah, no,
my bachelorette party's gonna be epic.
I love how I'm talking about it.
I'm not even engaged.
I think it's gonna happen soon.
-What's up, bitches?
-Who are you talking to?
-Look at you!
-Maya! Hi!
-[Maya] Christine.
-You look like the Joker.
Thank you. I feel like it all the time.
What are you doing?
[Maya] I'm in Miami,
then I'll be back in a few days.
Better be back in time
for my birthday, bitch.
-[Maya] I'll be there.
-Perfect.
-Yay! Party, party.
-[Christine] You better be there. Excited.
[Maya] Christine,
I'm digging the vibrant colors.
Thank you.
I was feeling very Harley Quinn.
You look super cute. Your boobs look huge.
-I know, right?
-[Heather] What's going on?
-I don't know. Just the bra, I think.
-[Heather scoffs]
-This lighting--
-[Maya] Alright, so…
I look really bad in this lighting.
-[Maya] I can't get rid of it.
-Oh my God.
♪ Oh I know exactly what I like ♪
♪ Oh I'm calling for you now it's time ♪
♪ Once I feel like this, feel like this
I'm not mad about it ♪
♪ 'Til I get my fix, get my fix
Gotta have it, have it ♪
[Chrishell] I just got a new listing
in the Valley.
The owner of Coldwater
reached out to me a few weeks ago.
[man over phone] It's Micky.
You dropped some of your materials off
at my construction site.
I was wondering if we could get together
and talk a little bit further
about my property.
I would absolutely love that.
-[man] Good morning.
-Hi, good morning.
-How are you? Good to see you.
-Good to see you in person.
How about we say 4.399?
-We have a deal. Thank you for coming.
-We have a deal.
This house is incredible,
but I have learned the hard way
that incredible houses
don't sell themselves.
I have to stay on my A game,
and the staging on this property
has got to be perfect.
♪ I'm all about it, I'm all about it ♪
[music fades out]
Hello.
Wow!
-Hi.
-Hi. This looks so good.
[Odelia] Thank you.
[Chrishell] I love these chairs.
I really love all the warm colors
you brought in
with the browns and the wood,
because it's just a lot of white.
I love how you did that.
Now I have to figure out how to copy this
when I'm at my house.
-Take a picture. [laughs]
-I know, I should.
Odelia has been staging homes
for a really long time,
and I, unfortunately,
just don't have that designer eye.
And I'm slowly learning,
because my husband, Justin,
and I bought our dream home
and I definitely need
to find some things to warm it up,
and to just kinda put
our own personal touch on it.
Then we'll add some wine in there.
When we sell the house,
we can have some of the wine.
Definitely.
[Odelia] Well,
we can take a look upstairs.
[Chrishell] Okay.
I can't wait to see what you did.
[Odelia] It's not finished completely.
Now we're gonna put a different sofa
with an animal rug
-and a coffee--
-Like, a little seating area here?
-[Odelia] Yeah.
-Okay, great.
[Odelia] And then we have the balcony.
It's huge.
[Chrishell] Oh, nice.
Beautiful day, beautiful view.
This is gonna be
one of my major selling points right here.
This house is gorgeous.
And just like Laurelwood,
it is going to have its own challenges
taking on another house of this caliber
because it is on a difficult street.
I need to find the right buyer, and I hope
since I got the owner down in price,
it won't be too difficult to sell.
["Rise Up" playing]
♪ We rise up
But stay down ♪
♪ They know it's on when we come around ♪
♪ We rise up
But back down ♪
♪ 'Cause we know what we got
When we got it like that♪
♪ We rise up
But we stay down… ♪
Hi, Monika.
-Hi, Christine.
-How are you?
I'm good, how are you?
Oh my God, so good--
-So good to see you.
-[Monika] So good seeing you too.
Monika came to me because she's looking
for marketing expertise.
And I feel like
she came to the right person,
because if there's anyone that knows
how to grab attention, it's me.
I've been doing some research
and thinking of really cool ways
that we can get people up to Mt. Olympus.
So I thought we should throw
a really, really cool event
just to get people there.
What do you think about a twilight?
I always like twilight.
I think that twilight's a great idea.
I kinda want to show you ideas,
because I've done a few parties in my day.
I like to do fun and interesting things,
like popcorn with me.
That's my face, obviously.
Then I've done lighters. That's my face.
We don't have to do that,
but I'm just saying,
flowers and candies and…
you know, like, really cool lights and…
-smoky cocktails.
-Maybe.
[Christine] I mean…
we don't have to have acrobats.
-[Christine] I had a zebra here--
-That's a bit, yeah, too much.
So no zebras. Okay. No zebras. Right.
So maybe, like, uh…
…like, peacocks?
Mm. Maybe no birds.
So no animals?
-[Monika] And then-- No animals.
-Okay.
I just want something more simple.
Maybe some cupcakes… food.
[Christine] Plain and simple
doesn't get the house sold.
I'm here to go over-the-top
and get some agents
into the broker's open.
Like-- You like burgers?
-I love-- Yeah, of course.
-Okay.
So then I had a twist on burgers,
and I thought,
"How cool would it be to get people there
with a really, really fun slogan?"
What if we did "Burgers and…
Botox"?
"Burgers and Botox."
I don't think you have to market
specifically for Botox,
'cause then it's gonna be known as
the Botox house, you know?
-[music comes to a halt]
-I'd love to live in a Botox house!
That pool would be my fountain of youth.
And I'd float. 'Cause of these jugs.
Perfect.
Let's do our best to kind of, you know,
come meet in the middle.
Let's make something fabulous
and just get this property sold.
-Definitely. I trust you…
-I'm excited.
-…not all the way, but I trust you.
-[both laughing]
["Olly Anna" playing]
♪ Never seen a girl like me
Never seen a girl like me, so free ♪
I bet you ain't never seen a girl like me♪
[music fades out]
-[Mary] How are you?
-Good, how are you?
[Maya] Nick Jonas just bought
in the Valley for 17 million, by the way.
On 15th, south of the Boulevard.
[Jason] And his brother, the other Jonas,
bought something too.
Joe. They both bought in the Valley.
Over ten million.
-[Maya] Yeah.
-[Jason] Hm.
The Valley. Interesting.
[Heather] Why isn't this working?
Do you guys know how to spell that word
cahoots, like, in cahoots?
-[Maya] What is cahoots?
-You know what it is.
-Cahoots?
-Like C-A-H-O-U-T-S?
-[Jason] C-A-H-O-O-T-S?
-[Heather] Yes.
I put C-A-H-U-T-E-S,
but Google's not working right now.
-What is cahoots?
-[Chrishell] It means you're in--
-Working together with someone.
-[Chrishell] … something with someone.
Cahoots. I never heard that.
In cahoots.
Like, they're in cahoots with each other.
[Heather] Oh, C-A-H-O-O-T-S.
Cahoots.
[Amanza] Hi.
-[Heather] Hi.
-How long have I worked here?
I still always-- Either push or pull,
I do the opposite
and, like, run into the door.
[Heather] Ladies, are you guys all going
to Christine's birthday?
Oh, yeah. Yeah, I'm going.
[Mary] Yeah.
-It'll be fun. Right?
-She said there is a tarot lady coming.
-Really?
-I'm curious to see.
[Brett] Are our invites coming by email,
-or how is that working?
-[Maya] I don't think you're invited.
-[Heather] No.
-[Maya] Girls only.
-[Brett] I'm just messing.
-Sorry. You wouldn't have fun anyways.
It's cool. It's probably true.
Jason and Brett aren't really into
tarot card reading.
I was never doing one. I never did one.
[Chrishell] One time
I got my tarot card reading,
she was like, "Oh, you have a big split
in your lifeline."
That puts a damper on things.
That was a long time ago,
so obviously it's not true.
You can't go to the tarot card reader
at the Kentucky County Fair.
[Jason] I'm willing to have
any conversation in this office,
but I cannot deal
with hearing about psychics.
Wait, I see this conversation ending.
-[all laughing]
-[Maya] Oh my God.
Does anyone know
why we have lines in our palms?
[Maya] I don't know.
[Amanza] So, they can move?
Yeah, but there's other lines
where they don't bend.
-Anything that bends has a crease.
-[Heather] Oh, wait.
You haven't talked to Christine, have you?
About anything?
Mm-mm.
-Not yet.
-[Amanza] You feel comfortable going
-to her party after…
-Mm…
It's gonna be awkward.
I mean, we haven't talked.
But I mean, I'm not gonna not go. But…
am I gonna wanna go to her birthday?
[scoffs]
Maybe to, uh…
give her a little birthday… cake.
[laughs]
-Do a-- Oh, Jesus. Okay.
-[Amanza] I'm kidding. No.
Maybe I'll just leave it as a…
[Mary] Maybe? Yeah.
I'll check the maybe box.
["Ordinary" playing]
♪ Feel like I'm in a new world
When I'm with ya ♪
♪ Do I, do I, do I like you
Like you… ♪
The Oppenheim Group
is getting more listings in Beverly Hills.
The homes are bigger, the land is bigger,
and the commission is bigger.
But the brokers are still small.
AKA Brett. [scoffs]
That's mean. Oh my God.
♪ You're classic, one of a kind ♪
♪ You're magic
There's nothing ordinary 'bout you ♪
[under breath] Oh, shit.
-I almost fell.
-[Brett] Hi. Nice.
[Heather] Story of my life. What's up?
-That's a nice little getup, right here.
-Thanks. Do I look like a boss?
[Brett] You do look like a boss. I might
let you boss me around in that outfit.
-Although I'm looking pretty boss-like.
-You'd like that, wouldn't you?
Is that a woman's suit or a man's suit?
[laughs]
Are you married to Santa Claus?
Shut up. This is hot.
It is hot, I'm just busting your boat.
[Heather] Okay, I gotta ask.
I've been hearing some rumors
that you're going on a date
with some chick, is this serious?
-Is it a big deal I'm going on a date?
-Yes. I've heard.
I am going on a date, yes.
It is a big deal because you don't date.
You don't do this.
-That's true.
-Are you nervous though?
No, I'm 42 yeas old. I'm an adult.
I can go on a date and not be nervous.
What, you wanna see me nervous?
I wanna see you, like,
get deep a little bit.
We'll see how it goes.
I don't know what to tell you.
If she's really cool,
then maybe I'll "get deep."
-Not in that way.
-Depending on… [laughs]
[Heather] My clients will be here soon.
They're driving up from Orange County.
They need a family home, so I think
this could be really good for them. Yay!
-Hi.
[Heather] Watch your feet in the grass.
-[Heather] Hi!
-Nice to see you.
-You too.
-Thanks for driving up here. Sorry.
-[man] Hi, nice to see you.
-Hi, thanks for coming up here.
-Come meet Brett.
-How's it going?
-Hey, how you doing? Pleasure to meet you.
-Good to meet you. Brett.
[woman] Nice to meet you.
-Thanks for driving up here.
-[Heather] They're friends of Tarek and…
they're looking to relocate up to LA
and Beverly Hills area.
[Brett] I love it. You got the hotel
about a hundred feet that way.
This is one of the biggest homes on
one of the biggest lots in all of 90210.
You've got
a full championship-size tennis court.
Basketball, as well.
Deep pool. It was built in the '80s,
so it's legit old-school deep pool.
Huge grass area.
The old owners had about 500 people here
at the after-parties for the Oscars.
You can entertain as much as you want.
You cover the pool
and you can just host any party you want.
It's really beautiful back here.
Help yourselves to the entire house.
Make yourselves at home.
-[woman] Okay. Thank you.
-[Heather] Alright, you guys.
[man] Pleasure.
[Brett] Look at the scale of this house
from here. I love this view of the house.
It has a little bit of work, to be honest
with you. The bathrooms need updating.
[Brett] We can talk about the bathrooms
when we talk about price.
I agree,
the bathrooms could be updated a little,
but the scale of the upstairs
is incredible.
-Yeah. Very roomy.
-The closet space
you were asking about, it's incredible.
[Heather] This is the living room. There's
two other great rooms to show you guys.
My relationship with Tarek
is still going very strong.
We split our time between West Hollywood
and down in Orange County.
I love living with him,
I love playing house,
but I'm still focusing on my career.
["Feels Like (Woohoohoohoohoo)" plays]
♪ When you got that thing
You got to own it… ♪
-[man] That chandelier's pretty amazing.
-[Heather] Isn't it? I can see if it comes
with the house.
Do you cook, Lauren? You do, right?
-[Lauren] I do.
-Is she good, Rene?
-She kills it in the kitchen.
-You better say that.
She does a really good job.
I love the gold accents,
I feel like it gives a very, like, sexy…
-vintage…
-I love these countertops.
-So this could be game room, playroom.
-[Lauren] Playroom.
-[Heather] Kinda like a everything room.
-[Rene] Oh wow.
-[Rene] I could see my office in here.
-Yeah? Big office, Rene, huh?
I love all the natural light in here too.
Right?
The house has great character, right?
I think we're a little stuck
on the style though.
I don't feel the, like, "This is the one."
[Heather] Okay, whatever.
Let's keep looking then.
-Thank you for coming.
-[Lauren] Thank you. Great to see you.
-I'll see you soon. Let's do dinner soon.
-[Rene] Great to see you.
We have interest in the house.
-Good.
-I have an agent that I work with,
but usually I do my own negotiations.
-So she's pretty good with it.
-Okay.
-I'm game with that.
-[man] I appreciate that.
We'll get something done. Alright?
Pleasure to meet you.
-[woman] Nice to meet you.
-Beautiful house.
-Glad you like it.
-Thank you.
[Brett] This is my colleague, Heather.
[all] Hi, nice to meet you.
-I'm Heather.
-Hi, Simon. nice to meet you.
-[Heather] What do they think of it?
-They like it.
-[Heather] Yeah?
-What's not to like?
Of course, Brett has a potential offer.
Brett's funny because Brett will, like,
sell a few homes
and then never come to the office
or take a little vacay.
And, like, Brett works hard,
but hardly works.
So…
["I'm Doing Me" playing]
♪ Look what am I doin'
I'm doin' me ♪
♪ Uh uh uh oh wo-o-o-o ♪
♪ Look what am I doin'
I'm doin' me ♪
-So cute. The skulls are so Christine.
-I know.
-Hi, guys.
-Hi.
♪ Save yourself the struggle
Cause there ain't nobody like me ♪
♪ Yeah that's how we do
You know that you feelin' it too ♪
-Hi!
-[Christine] Hi.
Don't get up, pregnant lady.
[Christine] Hi, ladies.
Of course,
I feel extremely hurt and offended
by Christine calling me a fucking idiot.
But I'm going to make an effort
and put on a happy face for her birthday.
[Maya] I just read today that the FDA said
that the silicone implants
are very highly cause of cancer.
-Silicone boobs?
-[Christine] I have saline.
[Maya] You have saline?
Fuck, I have silicone.
[Amanza] No, mine are silicone. Yeah.
-[Maya] I don't know, mine was--
-You guys are all getting recalled.
[Heather] Mine are saline…
[Christine] Oh, that catches on fire…
Love it.
-[Heather] That's what it is.
-[man] We use this…
-[Maya] Don't try this at home, ladies.
-How cute is that?
-[all] Cheers. Happy birthday, Christine.
-[laughter]
Oh, interesting.
Excuse me, is that one vegan?
-[Davina laughs] Okay.
-[woman] Davina…
Hey.
Are you my present?
-I am your present!
-Oh my God, I love you.
-[Christine] It's so nice to meet you.
-It's so good to meet you guys.
Davina thought it would be really great
for me to come and
for your birthday, tarot reading.
I also do hands.
We're gonna start with Christine
'cause it's her birthday.
Go like this with your hands really quick.
Do you see how your fingers do this?
-They bend right here.
-[Christine] Uh-huh.
So that is your power finger.
-Is that why I yell at bitches like this?
-[Mischel] Yes. But…
But…
-sometimes you bend for people.
-[Mary] Oh my God.
Like, over in the bedroom?
-Maybe.
-[Christine] I do that.
-[Mischel] You are very loyal.
-Very.
-[Davina] Yep.
-To a fault almost.
[Mischel] You hate drama.
Like, you really do.
You hate drama. No, it's true.
-[Heather] Yeah, she's right.
-Has Christine had a hand transplant?
[women laughing]
Just because you're good at something
doesn't mean you like it.
[Mischel] This is a part
of ultimate happiness.
I'm not sure how much Davina paid
for this "psychic,"
but she clearly needs
to get her money back.
Sorry.
Hey, you will have your turn.
Sit in your corner,
you will have your turn.
Okay. Oh!
[Christine gasps]
I love that card already. The devil.
So the devil's
about instant gratification.
-[Mischel] So…
-[women laughing]
[Mischel] I like her little giggle.
I think I need to do you next.
Oh, yeah!
[Mischel] Let's see…
[Mischel] Oh, of course.
You are super independent,
but the thing that keeps you
from actually figuring out
what makes you happy
is that you've disconnected
from your feelings.
You're really good at being like,
"I'm good, I'm fine."
-[Maya] Sound like you.
-[Davina] Does that sound right?
So the tarot card reader has informed me
that I'm very good at hiding my emotions.
I don't know that that's the case
with Christine and her bullshit.
[Mischel] Okay, you can relax.
So your need is passion.
-You need someone that adores you.
-[Davina] I think you got that.
Oh wow, you are super independent.
You have hands like a surgeon.
-[Mischel] Seriously.
-[Amanza] Thought it was my turn again.
Sometimes you're a little weird.
[Amanza repeating] Davina?
-[Christine] Oh, that is so true!
-[Chrishell] That is so true!
-[Amanza] Really?
-[Mischell] Okay. That's interesting. So…
you have two different emotional needs.
What's interesting about you
is that people meet this girl,
the "Hi!" Right?
[laughter]
And then when you get to know her,
it's more like, "Hey."
That's good.
-[Heather] I like that.
-[Maya] Yeah.
-Nice.
-[Chrishell] That's good.
So what she's saying
is Chrishell is two-faced.
Damn, that tarot reader's good.
[Mischel] In your work it's about passion.
You have to be excited,
it has to be interesting,
or you get bored.
In your personal life, you like freedom.
So, like, your home is your comfort oasis.
-Yes.
-[Mischel] Okay.
-[Heather] Do I get to pick a card?
-[Mischel] Yes.
-[all giggling]
-Oh my God, it's one of my favorite cards.
No, it really is. 'Cause it's so cute.
-It's an animal.
-So this is the card of speed.
So things are moving fast.
[Heather] True!
-[Christine repeating] Oh my God!
-[all clapping]
[Christine] This bitch meets someone
and she's like,
"We're getting married tomorrow,
we're in love."
Oh my God, that's perfect for you.
So ladies,
it was so nice to hang out with you all.
[all] Thank you.
-Happy birthday.
-[Christine] It was so wonderful.
I hope everybody learned something.
[all] Bye.
She's really, really good. Really good.
I like the fact that she said
you don't like drama.
The reality is I never start the drama,
I just finish it.
[Amanza] I think what happens is
a situation occurs, you react.
When you have time, you're like,
"Okay, maybe that wasn't
the best way to react."
-I disagree.
-[Amanza] And you don't--
But then you come and you go,
"Maybe I shouldn't have been,
like, this way. Maybe."
No, I disagree.
The way that I think about it…
-[Amanza] That's what it seems like.
-…is I'm like, "Maybe I shouldn't have
said it that harshly."
However, my feelings--
-How's that different?
-I don't regret what I said.
But delivery can change
the words completely, you know?
[Christine] Totally. Yeah.
It's not the way you say it,
it's how you say it. Right?
I agree. And sometimes I say things
because I'm so blunt and I'm so honest,
and I'm like,
"I just feel this way, and this way."
-So, you came to the bridal parlor…
-I don't know what you're talking about.
…and wanted to apologize for what
happened at the broker's open.
And you were like,
"It was just about, what happened
at the bachelorette party, blah, blah."
And I was like,
"Okay, I can see your side."
And I also see Mary's side.
And Mary's my best friend.
Tough situation.
Totally, I know.
And you wanna be there for your friend--
But then I go away from the situation
and then I hear at the wedding
that when you guys tried to talk it out,
you were like,
"She was acting like a fucking idiot."
-Who calls their friend a fucking idiot?
-I can call her whatever I want.
You can't call me whatever you want
and still expect to be friends, but…
I can call you whatever I want
if I feel that way.
-I said, "And still expect to be friends."
-I don't know at this point.
-I don't know what to say.
-All you keep saying is…
Didn't they talk about it?
[Mary] …what's the word?
[Davina] She came to the bridal shop
and I thought you talked about it then.
Oh, she didn't say,
"I called Mary a fucking idiot,
and now I'm apologizing for that."
You're such a liar.
Why would I come there to apologize
if I didn't own up to what I said?
We need to take this down a notch.
Like, Amanza, I love you,
and thank you so much.
Christine, this is your birthday party
and I don't agree
with what's going on right now,
but it's your birthday party
and we'll put a pin in it.
I love everybody,
and let's, please continue…
celebrating Christine's birthday.
Okay, babe? I love you.
Well, now I don't know if we can.
["Pretty Little Lies" playing]
♪ Do you believe
Or are they just pretty little lies? ♪
♪ Caught in a riptide
Lost in a sea ♪
♪ Of pretty little lies ♪